Guide to the Leah Fritz Papers, 1940-2009 and undated RL.10134
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings series, undated; 17 boxes
  - Book Reviews subseries, 1966-2001 and undated; 1 boxes
    - Among Women- Louise Berkinow, undated (Box 30)
    - The Anatomy of Freedom- Robin Morgan, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Beautiful Losers- Leonard Cohen, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Beginning to See the Light: Pieces of a Decade- Ellen Willis, 1981 (Box 30)
    - Black Macho and the Myth of the Superwoman- Michelle Wallace, circa 1978 (Box 30)
    - Book review and commentary for Sojourner, undated (Box 30)
    - A Company of Queens- Karen Lindsey, undated (Box 30)
    - The Complete Woman- Patricia Gundry, 1981 (Box 30)
    - Confirmation: An Anthology of African American Women- Amiri and Amina Baraka, 1983 (Box 30)
    - Depth Perception: New Poems and a Masque- Robin Morgan, 1982 (Box 30)
    - Digging Out- Anne Richardson, 1967 (Box 30)
    - Errata- Michael Donaghy, undated (Box 30)
    - For a New Novel- Alain Robbe-Grillet, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Gone to Soldiers- Marge Piercy, undated (Box 30)
    - Hammer and Tongues: A Dictionary of Women's WIt and Humour- Michelle Brown and Ann O'Connor, undated (Box 30)
    - High Crimes and Misdemeanors- Joanne Greenberg, 1980 (Box 30)
    - History: A Novel- Elsa Morante, undated (Box 30)
    - A Humming Under my Feet- Barbara Deming, 1985 (Box 30)
    - Lady of the Beast- Robin Morgan, undated (Box 30)
    - Love, Death, adn the Changing of Seasons- Marilyn Hacker, undated (Box 30)
    - La Maison de Rendezvous- Alain Robbe-Grillet, 1967 (Box 30)
    - Marilyn- Gloria Steinem, 1987 (Box 30)
    - Maureen Duffy, 1987 (Box 30)
    - Moving into the Space Cleared by our Mothers- Mary Dorcey, 1991 (Box 30)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Scotland are Dead: Poems 1980-1984- Kathleen Jamie, undated (Box 30)
    - Nobody Speaks for Me- Nancy Seifer, undated (Box 30)
    - Old Habits- Rhona McAdam, 1993 (Box 30)
    - Outrageous Acts and Everyday Rebellions- Gloria Steinem, 1983 (Box 30)
    - Parents, undated (Box 30)
    - Pornography: Men Possessing Women- Andrea Dworkin, 1981 (Box 30)
    - A Responsibility to Awe- Rebecca Elson, 2001 (Box 30)
    - Robin Morgan, undated (Box 30)
    - The Spiral Staircase- Adam Johnson, undated (Box 30)
    - Thinking of Skins- Carol Rumens, 1993 (Box 30)
    - With Child- Phyllis Chesler, 1979 (Box 30)
    - The Woman of the Wolf and Other Stories- Renee Vivian, 1984 (Box 30)
    - Woman's Creation- Elizabeth Fisher, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Women, Money, and Power- Phyllis Chesler, undated (Box 30)
- Audiotapes series, 1980-1988 and undated; 1 boxes
  The Audiotapes series contains audiocassettes of presentations and poetry readings by Fritz and other recordings. Cassettes labeled with poets' names presumably contain recordings of poetry readings, interviews, or other content related to those poets and their works.
  Alphabetical by cassette label.
  - Cambridge Forum: Issues for Action- Women's Empowerment Without Men? Fritz, Lindsay 5/21/80, 1980; 1
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0001)
  - Carol Rumens, Jyoti Patel, Meera Syal, undated; 2
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0002)
  - Clair Chapman- Spare Tyre / Olwen Wymark, undated; 3
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0003)
  - From Cookie to Witch is an Old Story, Written and Read by Leah Fritz / Mary Dorcey, undated; 4
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0004)
  - Jenny McLeod, Winsome Pinnock / Kate Howard, Carol Rumens, undated; 5
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0005)
  - Leila Hassan, Helen Webb / Helen Webb, Olwen Wymark, undated; 6
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0006)
  - Mary Dorcey, undated; 7
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0007)
  - Pam Gems, undated; 8
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0008)
  - Pen Diary 4/88, 1988; 9
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0009)
  - Women's Theatre Group / Yana Stajno, undated; 10
    - Original audiocassette (Box 32, Audio-cassette RL10134_CS_0010)